// src/data/questions.js
export const questions = [{
        question: "Who puts his head in a turkey on Thanksgiving??",
        options: [" Ross", "Monica", "Joey", "Chandler"],
    },
    {
        question: "How many sisters does Joey have? ",
        options: ["Five", "Three", "Six", "Seven"],
        answer: "Seven",
    },

    {
        question: "How many kids does Ross have?  ",
        options: ["Three", "Two", "One", "0"],
        answer: "Two",
    },

    {
        question: "What is the name of Joey's stuffed penguin?  ",
        options: ["Hugsy", "Michel", "Chucky", "Dora"],
        answer: "Hugsy",
    },

    {
        question: "What did Phoebe name the rat in her apartment? ",
        options: ["Anie", "Bob", "Peter", "Alice"],
        answer: "Bob",
    },

    {
        question: "Phoebe stole a comic book from Ross. What was the name of the book?  ",
        options: ["Smart Boy", "Science World", "Science Boy", "Space Boy"],
        answer: "Science Boy",
    },
    {
        question: "Who was Monica's first kiss with?",
        options: ["Joey", "Chandler", "Richard", "Ross"],
        answer: "Ross",
    },

    {
        question: "Which brand offers Rachel a job in Paris? ",
        options: ["Gucci", "Louis Vuitton", "Ralph Lauren", "Chanel"], // Ensure these are strings
        answer: "Louis Vuitton",
    },


    {
        question: "Which of the friends hates Thanksgiving?   ",
        options: ["Rachel", "Joey", "Ross", "Chandler"],
        answer: "Chandler",
    },


    {
        question: "What store does Phoebe hate?  ",
        options: ["IKEA", "Willams Scnoma", "Pottery Barn", "WayFair"],
        answer: "Pottery Barn",
    },

    {
        question: "What is Ross's profession?  ",
        options: ["Geoscientist", "Archaeologist", "Paleontologist", "Zoologist"],
        answer: "Paleontologist",
    },
    {
        question: "What was Ross and Rachel's daughter's first word?  ",
        options: ["Jack", "Gleba", "Monica", "Hello"],
        answer: "Gleba",
    },
    {
        question: "At the diner she worked at, how much did Pete Becker tip Monica?  ",
        options: ["$10,000", "$20,000", "$1,000", "$2,000"],
    },
    {
        question: "As a child, Rachel had a dog. What was its name?  ",
        options: ["Dragon", "Marcel", "LaPooh", "Chi-Chi"],
        answer: "LaPooh",
    },


];